Braide Daniella Biobele

Frontend Developer

🔀 dannygodwin2003@gmail.com 📞 08020554163 😲 Port Harcourt, Nigeria 🜎 Github 💆 Twitter

in LinkedIn

Profile

A Frontend Web Developer experienced in HTML, CSS, Javascript, etc to make functional, Interactive, and Responsive websites. Having a vast knowledge of Figma helps me work with designers. Uses GitHub to collaborate with other developers. Really do look forward to working with you and giving my best.

Experience

06/2022 - present Port Harcourt, Nigeria

Frontend Web Development Intern

Harvoxx Tech Hub ☑

- · Underwent four months of intensive training.
- Got involved in a list of mini-projects given to me by my tutors.
- Transformed Figma prototypes into functional User Interfaces using HTML, CSS & JavaScript.
- Started working on a project with a team as the frontend web developer.

09/2022 - present Nigeria

Frontend Web Development Intern

Zuri & I4G 🛮

- Underwent intensive training for 3 months on Frontend web development.
- Started working on a project(Alumni Donate) with a team as a front-end web developer.
- Collaborated with other front-end developers on the team to build the site.

Education

11/2019 - present Portharcourt, Nigeria

Electronics and Computer Engineering

University of Portharcourt

Technologies

HTML, CSS, Javascript, SASS, React, Tailwind

Tools

Figma, VS Code, Github, Slack, Notion, Photoshop

Soft skills

Communication, Team spirit